hippieshop.com 2004-12-04

# Hippie Shop - , Hippie Clothes & Gifts at discount prices!

**FREE GIFT: We would like to wish everyone a Happy Hippy Holiday!  
All orders placed in December will include a FREE Tie-Dye HippieShop.com Pen.**

**Privacy Policy**

**Our Pledge to You, Our Customer**

HippieShop.com respects your privacy. HippieShop.com does not sell, rent, or loan any identifiable information regarding its customers to any third party. Any information you give us is held with the utmost care and security, and will not be used in ways to which you have not consented. 

When you purchase products from HippieShop.com or register for any HippieShop.com services, we may automatically place you on our list to receive e-mail regarding updates about special offers, new products, and new services. If you do not wish to receive e-mail updates, please send an e-mail to [remove@hippieshop.com](mailto:remove@hippieshop.com) and type "remove" in the subject line. 

**Use of Information**

HippieShop.com will not collect any personal information about individuals except when specifically and knowingly provided by such individuals. Examples of such information are: name, postal address, e-mail address, phone number, birthdays, and product commentary.

HippieShop.com may share non-personal aggregate, or summary, information regarding its customers with partners or other third parties, but HippieShop.com does not sell or share any information at the individual customer level. 

**Cookies**

HippieShop.com uses a feature of your Internet Web browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. HippieShop.com creates and then uses these cookie files to track your clicks as you go through the HippieShop.com Web site. 

HippieShop.com only uses cookies to keep track of items you put into your shopping cart, to tell us whether you have visited HippieShop.com previously, and to help us determine whether you came to HippieShop.com from a particular Internet link or banner advertisement. 

Cookies can also be used to help to save and retrieve passwords used on the HippieShop.com site and information on past purchases and other preferences, saving you from having to re-enter this information upon every visit to the HippieShop.com Web site. Cookies cannot be used by HippieShop.com to retrieve any personal information about you unless you have previously purchased from or registered with HippieShop.com. HippieShop.com does not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer unless such information was knowingly and willingly provided by you. 

If you have further questions about HippieShop.com's privacy policy, [email us.](mailto:info@hippieshop.com)
